Firelight Team : firelight.blog.ir
Instagram: fire._.light.sub
BLACKPINK : blackpink.blog.ir
ENGLISH SUB by ●•▪Sajedeh▪•●
Instagram: fire._.light.sub
Endless night
Love trapped us in a windowless room
What can we say
Long for love even though it hurts every time
Get hurt and break down I
don’t know what’s keeping me to hold on
If I leave anyway, I’ll hate you in my pained state
We can’t end it before it’s over
It’s as if we’ve been waiting for this agony
Maybe it’s all just for a moment
What are we looking for so aimlessly
But I don’t care I’ll do it over and over
I just need you in my life
We are the lovesick girls
You can’t just end this love on your own
I’m nothing without this pain
But we were born to be alone
Yeah we were born to be alone
But why we still looking for love
No love letters, no x and o’s
No love never, my exes know
No diamond rings, that set in stone
To the left, better left alone
Didn’t wanna be a princess, I’m priceless
A prince not even on my list
Love is a drug that I quit
No doctor could help when I’m lovesick
Maybe it’s all just for a moment
What are we looking for so aimlessly
Looking at you with my anxious gaze
You’re all I need even if it hurts
We are the lovesick girls
You can’t just end this love on your own
I’m nothing without this pain
But we were born to be alone
Yeah we were born to be alone
But why we still looking for love
Love is slippin’ and fallin’
Love is killin’ your darlin’
That fearless thrill returns once the pain subsides
Can’t hear what you say
I’m happy with this pain
You pity me, but I pity you more for pitying me
We are the lovesick girls
You can’t just end this love on your own
I’m nothing without this pain
Lovesick girls
Everyone eventually leaves
I’ve become numb to crying
Lovesick girls
Hurt over and over again
But we’re still looking for love
FIRELIGHT: firelight.blog.ir
BLACKPINK : blackpink.blog.ir
ENGLISH SUB by ●•▪Sajedeh▪•●
Instagram: fire._.light.sub